Guide to the Yale Classes Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale classes photographs
1806-1971
RU 779
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
129.35
(95 boxes)
The materials consist of formal portraits, group portraits, and reunion photographs of students and graduates of Yale College, Yale School of Law, Yale School of Divinity, Yale School of Medicine and the Sheffield Scientific School.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Class of 1909 freshman photograph gift of Nathan Marks, 2013. Accession 2017-A-059 gift of Anne Hall Connor, 2017. Accession 2018-A-047 gift of Carol Bertrand, 2017.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-A (YRG 10-A), Records of Yale College classes.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged in three series: I. Pictures of Yale Classes, 1806-1971. II. Oversize Pictures of Yale Classes, 1852-1970. III. Folio Pictures of Yale Classes, 1856-1960., and one addition.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of formal portraits, group portraits, and reunion photographs of students and graduates of Yale College, Yale School of Law, Yale School of Divinity, Yale School of Medicine, and the Sheffield Scientific School.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Photographs; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School -- Students
- Pictures of Yale Classes, 1806-1971; Series I
  - Class of 1806: Individual profile
    Separated Materials
    Transfered to RU 684, Series 1, Box 14, Folder 536.
  - Class of 1817: 50th Reunion, 1867 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1830: 55th Reunion, 1885 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1832: Individual portraits (later) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1840: 60th Reunion, 1900 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1843: Individual portraits (later) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1844: Individual portraits (later) (Box 1, Folder 7-10)
  - Class of 1848: Individual portraits (Abbe-unidentified) (Box 1, Folder 11-14)
  - Class of 1849: Individual portraits (Box 3, Box 2, Folder 15-23)
  - Class of 1850: Individual portraits (later) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Class of 1851
    - Dagguerotypes: Brownson, Cone, Crampton, Hollister, Hughes, Jessup, Gallup, Mead, Peet, Stiles, Temple (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Individual portraits (Box 4, Folder 25-27)
  - Class of 1852
    - 35th Reunion, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 50th Reunion, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - 60th Reunion, 1912 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Class of 1853
    - Small group, 1853 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Individual portraits (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Reunion--10th or 15th, 1863-1868 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Key to 25th Reunion photo, 1873 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - 50th Reunion (+ Key), 1903 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Class of 1854
    - 40th Reunion, 1894 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Reunion--probably 50th, 1904 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Class of 1855
    - Class picture/Reunion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Class of 1856: Reunion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Class of 1857: Reunion, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Class of 1858
    - Individual portraits (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    - Individual portraits (Box 5, Folder 38-45)
    - 3 members: Kimball, Potter, and Van Name 50th Reunion (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Class of 1860
    - Individual portrait (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 35th Reunion, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - 40th Reunion, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Class of 1861
    - 50th Reunion, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - 55th Reunion, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Class of 1862
    - 45th Reunion, 1907 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - 50th Reunion, 1912 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Class of 1863
    - Students on fence (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Individual portraits (Box 6, Folder 51-54)
    - 45th Reunion, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - 50th Reunion, 1913 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - 55th Reunion, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Class of 1864
    - Small group (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Small groups (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Individual portraits (later) (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - 60th Reunion, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Class of 1865
    - Class picture (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Individual portraits (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Individual portraits (Box 7, Folder 62-67)
    - Individual portraits (Box 8, Folder 68-69)
    - Reunion, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Class of 1866
    - Class picture (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Individual portraits (Box 8, Folder 72-76)
  - Class of 1867
    - Class picture (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - Individual portraits (Box 9, Folder 78-82)
    - Individual portraits (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - 30th Reunion, 1897 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - 40th Reunion, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - 50th Reunion, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Class of 1868
    - Class pictures (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Small groups (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - On fence (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Individual portraits (including one tintype) (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - Individual portraits (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - 25th Reunion, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - [Class picture] fine art (Box 10, Folder 87)
  - Class of 1868s: Class picture (Box 10, Folder 88)
  - Class of 1869
    - Class pictures (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - Students on fence (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - 50th Reunion, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - Hopkins Grammar School, 1865 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Class of 1869s
    - 40th Reunion, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Class of 1870
    - Class Pictures (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - 20th Reunion, 1890 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - 50th Reunion, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Class of 1871
    - Class picture (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Individual portraits (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Individual portraits (Box 10, Folder 95-97)
    - Individual portraits (Box 11, Folder 98-101)
    - 40th Reunion headquarters, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 101)
    - 45th Reunion, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 102)
    - 50th Reunion, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 103)
    - Assorted later snapshots (Box 11, Folder 104)
  - Class of 1871s
    - 40th Reunion, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - 50th Reunion, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 105)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 11, Folder 105)
  - Class of 1872
    - Class picture (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Students in chapel (Box 11, Folder 106)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 11, Folder 107)
  - Classes of 1872 & 1873: Individual portraits (mostly 1872) (Box 11, Folder 108-110)
  - Class of 1873
    - Individual portraits (Box 12, Folder 111-113)
    - 45th (?) Reunion, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - 50th Reunion, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - 55th (?) Reunion, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 12, Folder 114)
    - Picture of A Survivor's Cup (Box 12, Folder 115)
  - Class of 1873s: Class picture (Box 12, Folder 116)
  - Class of 1874
    - Class pictures (Box 12, Folder 117)
    - 25th Reunion, 1899 (Box 12, Folder 118-119)
    - 30th Reunion, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - 35th Reunion, 1909 (Box 12, Folder 120)
    - 40th Reunion, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - 45th Reunion, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - 50th Reunion, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 121)
    - 55th Reunion, 1929 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - Class of 1874s: Small group (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Class of 1875
    - Class pictures (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Individual photograph (informal) (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - Newspaper clipping (Box 13, Folder 124)
    - 30th Reunion, 1905 (Box 13, Folder 125)
    - 40th Reunion, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - 50th Reunion, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Class of 1875s
    - Individual portraits (Box 13, Folder 127)
    - 25th Reunion, 1901 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - 50th Reunion, 1925 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - 55th Reunion, 1930 (Box 13, Folder 128)
    - 60th Reunion, 1935 (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Class of 1876
    - Class picture (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Picture of class paraphernalia (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Hadley (Yale President) grave (Box 13, Folder 130)
    - Individual portraits (Box 13, Folder 131)
    - Individual portraits (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - Assorted snapshots (including one tintype) (Box 13, Folder 132)
    - 20th Reunion, 1896 (Box 13, Folder 133)
    - 25th Reunion, 1901 (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Class of 1876 & 1876s
    - 35th Reunion, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - 40th Reunion, 1916 (Box 13, Folder 134)
    - 45th Reunion, 1921 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - 50th Reunion, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 135)
    - 55th Reunion, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 136)
    - Informal shot (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Class of 1877
    - Class pictures (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Students on fence (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Small group (Box 14, Folder 137)
    - Letter from Harvard (Box 14, Folder 138-139)
    - Individual portraits (Box 14, Folder 139)
    - 15th Reunion, 1892 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - 25th Reunion, 1902 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - 30th Reunion, 1907 (Box 14, Folder 140)
    - 35th Reunion, 1912 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - 40th Reunion, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - 50th Reunion, 1927 (Box 14, Folder 142)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Class of 1878
    - Class pictures (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Students on fence (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - Photograph of William Howard Taft (Box 15, Folder 144)
    - 20th Reunion, 1898 (Box 15, Folder 145)
    - 25th Reunion, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 146)
    - 30th Reunion, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 147-149)
    - 35th Reunion, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - 40th Reunion, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 150)
    - 45th Reunion, 1923 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - 50th Reunion, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 151)
    - 55th Reunion, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 152)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 15, Folder 152)
  - Class of 1878s
    - Class Picture (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - 25th Reunion, 1903 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - 30th Reunion, 1908 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - 40th Reunion, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 153)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 15, Folder 154)
  - Class of 1879
    - Class pictures (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Students on the fence (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Small group (Box 16, Folder 155)
    - Class trophies (Box 16, Folder 156)
    - Individual portraits (Box 16, Folder 157-158)
    - 20th Reunion, 1899 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - 25th Reunion, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 159)
    - 30th Reunion, 1908 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - 40th Reunion, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - 55th (?) Reunion, 1923 (Box 16, Folder 160)
    - 60th Reunion, 1928 (Box 16, Folder 161)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 16, Folder 162)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 16, Folder 162)
  - Class of 1879s: Small groups (Box 16, Folder 163)
  - Class of 1880
    - Class picture (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - Students on the fence (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - Individual portrait and assorted snapshots (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - 15th Reunion, 1895 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - 20th Reunion, 1900 (Box 16, Folder 164)
    - 25th Reunion, 1905 (Box 16, Folder 165)
    - 30th Reunion, 1910 (Box 16, Folder 166)
    - 40th Reunion, 1920 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - 45th Reunion, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - 50th Reunion, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 167)
    - 55th Reunion, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - Class of 1880s
    - Class picture (Box 16, Folder 168)
    - 35th Reunion, 1915 (Box 16, Folder 169)
    - 45th Reunion, 1925 (Box 16, Folder 169)
  - Class of 1881
    - Class pictures (Box 17, Folder 170)
    - Students on fence (Box 17, Folder 170)
    - Class Boy (Box 17, Folder 170)
    - 20th Reunion, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 171)
    - 25th Reunion, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 171)
    - 30th Reunion, 1911 (Box 17, Folder 172)
    - 35th Reunion, 1916 (Box 17, Folder 173)
    - Reunion (list only), 1919 (Box 17, Folder 174)
    - 40th Reunion, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - 45th Reunion, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - 50th Reunion, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 175)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Class of 1881 Law (?) Students and Faculty (Box 17, Folder 176)
  - Class of 1881s
    - Class picture (Box 17, Folder 176)
    - 20th Reunion, 1901 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - 25th Reunion, 1906 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - 40th Reunion, 1921 (Box 17, Folder 177)
    - 45th Reunion, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - 50th Reunion, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - 1934 Reunion (Box 17, Folder 178)
    - 55th Reunion, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - 60th Reunion, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 179)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Class of 1882
    - Class pictures (Box 17, Folder 180)
    - Small group (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - Individual portrait (later) (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - 30th Reunion, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 181)
    - 35th Reunion, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - 45th Reunion, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - 50th Reunion, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 182)
    - 55th Reunion, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 183)
    - 60th Reunion, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 183)
  - Class of 1882s
    - Individual portraits (Box 18, Folder 184-186)
    - 10th Reunion, 1892 (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - 25th Reunion, 1907 (Box 18, Folder 187)
    - 30th Reunion, 1912 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - 35th Reunion, 1917 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - 40th Reunion, 1922 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - 45th Reunion, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - 50th Reunion, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 188)
    - 55th Reunion, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - 60th Reunion, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - Class of 1883
    - Class pictures (Box 18, Folder 189)
    - Students on fence (Box 18, Folder 190)
    - Small group (Box 18, Folder 190)
    - Trophies (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - Play cast photos (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - Eating Clubs (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - 15th Reunion, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 191)
    - Bicentennial, 1901 (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - Taft Dinner (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - 20th Reunion, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 192)
    - 15th Reunion, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 193)
    - 25th Reunion, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - 30th Reunion, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 194)
    - 35th Reunion, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - 40th Reunion, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 195)
    - 35th Reunion, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - 50th Reunion, 1943 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - 45th Reunion, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - 60th (?) Reunion, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 196)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 19, Folder 197)
  - Class of 1883s
    - Small groups (Box 19, Folder 197)
    - 20th Reunion, 1903 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - 35th Reunion, 1918 (Box 19, Folder 198)
    - 45th Reunion, 1928 (Box 19, Folder 199)
    - 50th Reunion, 1933 (Box 19, Folder 199)
    - 55th Reunion, 1938 (Box 19, Folder 200)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 19, Folder 200)
  - Class of 1884
    - Class picture (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - Small group (Box 19, Folder 201)
    - Individual portraits (Box 19, Folder 202)
    - Individual portraits (Box 20, Folder 203-207)
    - 1901 Reunion (Box 20, Folder 207)
    - 20th Reunion, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 208)
    - 25th Reunion, 1909 (Box 20, Folder 209)
    - 30th Reunion, 1914 (Box 21, Folder 210)
    - 40th Reunion, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - 45th Reunion, 1929 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - 50th Reunion, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 211)
    - 55th Reunion, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 21, Folder 212)
  - Class of 1884s
    - Class picture (Box 21, Folder 212)
    - Individual portraits (Box 21, Folder 213)
    - Individual portraits (Box 21, Folder 214-216)
    - 40th Reunion, 1924 (Box 21, Folder 217)
  - Class of 1885
    - Class pictures (Box 21, Folder 217)
    - Drawing (Box 21, Folder 218)
    - Students on fence (Box 21, Folder 219)
    - Students on fence (Box 21, Folder 219)
    - Individual portrait (Box 21, Folder 219)
    - Small groups (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - Triennial, 1888 (Box 22, Folder 220)
    - 20th Reunion, 1905 (Box 22, Folder 221)
    - 25th Reunion, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 221)
    - Reunion, 1905 -1915 (Box 22, Folder 222)
    - Reunion, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 222)
    - Reunion, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 223)
    - 30th Reunion, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 224)
    - 40th Reunion, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 224)
    - 50th Reunion, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 225)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 22, Folder 225)
  - Class of 1885 Divinity
    - Class picture (Box 22, Folder 226)
  - Class of 1885 & 1885s
    - Class pictures (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - Small groups (Box 22, Folder 227)
    - 15th (?) Reunion, 1900 (Box 22, Folder 228)
    - 25th Reunion, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 228)
    - 30th Reunion, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 229)
    - 35th Reunion, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 229)
    - 40th Reunion, 1925 (Box 22, Folder 229)
    - 45th Reunion, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 230)
    - 55th Reunion, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 230)
    - 50th Reunion, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 231)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - Class of 1886
    - Class pictures (Box 23, Folder 232)
    - Students on fence (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Small group (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Class Day (Box 23, Folder 233)
    - Individual portraits (Box 23, Folder 234-241)
    - Individual portrait (Box 24, Folder 242-252)
    - 10th Reunion, 1896 (Box 25, Folder 253)
    - 20th Reunion, 1906 (Box 25, Folder 253)
    - Reunions, 1906-1931 (Box 25, Folder 253)
    - 30th Reunion, 1916 (Box 25, Folder 254)
    - 45th Reunion, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 254)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 25, Folder 254)
  - Class of 1887
    - Class pictures (Box 25, Folder 255)
    - Students on fence (Box 25, Folder 255)
    - Small groups (Box 25, Folder 255)
    - Class Day (Box 25, Folder 256)
    - Individual portrait (Box 25, Folder 256)
    - Individual portrait (Box 25, Folder 257-264)
    - Individual portraits (Box 26, Folder 265-272)
    - Reunion, 1895 (Box 26, Folder 273)
    - 20th Reunion, 1907 (Box 26, Folder 274)
    - 25th Reunion, 1912 (Box 26, Folder 274)
    - 30th Reunion, 1917 (Box 26, Folder 275)
    - 35th Reunion, 1922 (Box 26, Folder 275)
    - 40th Reunion, 1927 (Box 26, Folder 275)
    - 45th Reunion, 1932 (Box 26, Folder 276)
    - 55th Reunion, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 276)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 26, Folder 276)
    - Assorted snapshots (later) (Box 26, Folder 277)
  - Class of 1887
    - Small group (Box 26, Folder 278)
  - Class of 1887s
    - 50th Reunion, 1937 (Box 26, Folder 279)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 26, Folder 279)
  - Class of 1888
    - Class pictures (Box 27, Folder 280)
    - Individual portraits (Box 27, Folder 281-290)
    - 40th Reunion, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 291)
    - 45th Reunion, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 291)
    - 60th Reunion, 1948 (Box 27, Folder 292)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 27, Folder 292)
  - Class of 1888s
    - 40th Reunion, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 293)
    - 45th Reunion, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 293)
  - Class of 1889
    - Class picture (Box 28, Folder 294)
    - Students on fence (1889?) (Box 28, Folder 294)
    - Small groups (Box 28, Folder 294)
    - Individual portraits (unidentified) (Box 28, Folder 295-301)
    - Individual portraits (unidentified) (Box 29, Folder 302-305)
    - Individual portraits (identified) (Box 29, Folder 306-313)
    - Individual portraits (identified) (Box 30, Folder 314-319)
    - Sexennial, 1895 (Box 30, Folder 320)
    - 10th Reunion, 1899 (Box 30, Folder 320)
    - 15th Reunion, 1904 (Box 30, Folder 320)
    - 20th Reunion, 1909 (Box 30, Folder 321)
    - 25th Reunion, 1914 (Box 30, Folder 322)
    - Yale-Harvard Luncheon, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 322)
    - 30th Reunion, 1919 (Box 30, Folder 322)
    - 35th Reunion, 1924 (Box 30, Folder 323)
    - 45th Reunion, 1929 (Box 30, Folder 323)
    - 55th Reunion, 1938 (Box 30, Folder 323)
    - 50th Reunion, 1934 (Box 30, Folder 324)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 30, Folder 324)
  - Class of 1889s
    - Class picture (Box 30, Folder 324)
    - Small groups (Box 31, Folder 325)
    - Informal shot (Box 31, Folder 325)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 31, Folder 326)
  - Class of 1890
    - Class pictures (Box 31, Folder 327)
    - Students on fence (Box 31, Folder 327)
    - Picnic, 1888 (Box 31, Folder 327)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1900 (Box 31, Folder 328)
    - 15th Reunion, 1905 (Box 31, Folder 328)
    - 20th Reunion, 1910 (Box 31, Folder 329)
    - 25th Reunion, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 329)
    - 30th Reunion, 1920 (Box 31, Folder 329)
    - 35th Reunion, 1925 (Box 31, Folder 330)
    - 45th Reunion, 1935 (Box 31, Folder 330)
    - 50th Reunion, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 330)
    - Reunion, 1942 (Box 31, Folder 331)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 31, Folder 331)
  - Class of 1890 Divinity: Class picture (Box 31, Folder 332)
  - Class of 1890s
    - Class pictures (Box 31, Folder 333)
    - 25th Reunion, 1915 (Box 31, Folder 334)
    - 50th Reunions, 1940 (Box 31, Folder 334)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 31, Folder 334)
  - Class of 1891
    - Class pictures (Box 31, Folder 335)
    - Class Day (Box 31, Folder 335)
    - Small Group (Box 31, Folder 335)
    - 10th Reunion, 1901 (Box 32, Folder 336)
    - 15th Reunion, 1906 (Box 32, Folder 336)
    - 20th Reunion, 1911 (Box 32, Folder 336)
    - 25th Reunion, 1916 (Box 32, Folder 337)
    - 30th Reunion, 1921 (Box 32, Folder 337)
    - 35th Reunion, 1926 (Box 32, Folder 337)
    - 40th Reunion, 1931 (Box 32, Folder 338)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 32, Folder 338)
    - Assorted snapshots (later) (Box 32, Folder 339)
  - Class of 1891-- Divinity: Class picture (Box 32, Folder 340)
  - Class of 1891 Law: Class picture Faculty & students (Box 32, Folder 341)
  - Class of 1891s
    - Class picture (Box 32, Folder 341)
    - Small group (Box 32, Folder 342)
    - Individual portraits (Box 32, Folder 343)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 32, Folder 343)
  - Class of 1892
    - Class picture (Box 32, Folder 344)
    - Small groups (Box 32, Folder 344)
    - Individual portraits (Box 32, Folder 344)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1895 (Box 32, Folder 345)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1898 (Box 32, Folder 345)
    - 10th Reunion, 1902 (Box 33, Folder 346)
    - 20th Reunion, 1912 (Box 33, Folder 346)
    - 15th Reunion, 1917 (Box 33, Folder 346)
    - 25th Reunion, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - 30th Reunion, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - 35th Reunion, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 347)
    - 45th Reunion, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 348)
    - 40th Reunion, 1937 (Box 33, Folder 348)
    - 45th Reunion, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 348)
    - 50th (?) Reunion, 1947 (Box 33, Folder 349)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 33, Folder 349)
    - Assorted snaphots (later) (Box 33, Folder 349)
  - Class of 1892s
    - Freshmen picture (Box 33, Folder 350)
    - Chemistry group (Box 33, Folder 350)
    - 50th Reunion, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 350)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 33, Folder 350)
  - Class of 1893
    - Class pictures (Box 33, Folder 351)
    - Small groups (Box 33, Folder 352)
    - Snapshots (recreation) (Box 33, Folder 352)
    - Individual portraits (Box 33, Folder 353)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1899 (Box 33, Folder 354)
    - 10th Reunion, 1903 (Box 33, Folder 354)
    - 15th Reunion, 1908 (Box 33, Folder 354)
    - 20th Reunion, 1913 (Box 33, Folder 355)
    - 25th Reunion, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 355)
    - 30th Reunion, 1923 (Box 33, Folder 355)
    - 35th Reunion, 1928 (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - 40th Reunion, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - 45th Reunion, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 356)
    - 50th Reunion, 1943 (Box 34, Folder 357)
    - 55th Reunion, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 357)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 34, Folder 358)
  - Class of 1893s
    - Class picture Reunion, Undated (Box 34, Folder 359)
  - Class of 1894
    - Class pictures (Box 34, Folder 360)
    - Individual portraits (Box 34, Folder 361-363)
    - Small group (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - Ambulance donated in WW I (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - War Photos (Box 34, Folder 364)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1904 (Box 34, Folder 365)
    - 35th Reunion, 1929 (Box 34, Folder 365)
    - 45th Reunion, 1939 (Box 34, Folder 365)